I'm beat.
My body's burning up.
I'm still alive, but at this
rate, I won't be for long.
Nobody's here.
An abandoned ship.
Full of.
Broken wood and scrap iron.
Funny huh?
Fit right in.
I gotta do something about this!
This useless body of mine,
I'm not gonna make it.
I'll see you
next time.
So, did you hear the news?
They're talking about it all over.
Tom's violent apprentice,
Kaido Flan, is dead.
He was hit by the Sea Train.
Iceberg, listen.
I know you can do it.
You're the first apprentice of Tom,
the greatest shipwright
the world has ever known.
If anybody can do it, you can.
Hey, Kokoro, one of these
days, let's share a drink.
You know when we actually have
something to drink to yeah Tom
I won't let you down I'll watch
over your dreams I'll protect
everything not only this town
but these blueprints as well hmm
there's a visitor sir he said
he's a friend from years back.
Do you know anyone named Kaido Flam?
Franky?
Shall I show him in, sir?
No.
Turn him away.
You sure picked a roundabout
way of meeting me.
Well, maybe.
But anyway, what's up with that
strange-looking body of yours?
Screw you!
The Sea Train mangled my body.
so in order to stay alive, I
rebuilt it using some iron scraps.
But that's not the issue!
I've heard that your
company's been contracted
to build ships for the world government!
I won't tolerate you doing
anything to help them!
How could you?
They took Tom away!
And the weapons that
caused the whole incident?
Have you forgotten who made those?
I'm sure you have plenty of things you want
to say to me, but I have a few as well.
I still haven't forgiven you.
Four years isn't nearly
enough time for that.
I'm surprised you even
have the nerve to show
your face around here after what happened.
What'd you say government
told me that you died
in an accident on the
railway you never came back?
So I believed it to be true
even if Tom forgave you
remember this it doesn't mean
for a second that I'm going to
What's with all the
secrecy something going on?
Hey, what are these?
The blueprints for that old battleship?
Don't call yourself Kaido Flam anymore.
It's only a matter of time
before the government targets me.
Now listen carefully.
I want you to take these and
leave this island, Franky.
Why should I?
The Kaido Flam from Tom's Workers is dead.
As long as you don't
use that name anymore,
then there'll be no connection between us.
Additionally,
if you leave the island, the whereabouts
of the blueprints will vanish.
Hey, hold on a second.
What happens if the government comes
after you and you don't have them?
I've said what I came to say. What the?
Hey, Iceberg!
We shouldn't see each other again.
Wait, hold on!
Listen to me.
Do you want to end up the
same way that Tom did?
Hang on to those blueprints.
If you're threatened and your life
is in danger, just hand them over.
And if you don't want to do that, you
can burn them right before their eyes.
If you were me would you
do that tom had achieved
so many wonderful things
but he gave up everything
To keep these blueprints
hidden from the world as
long as the risk remains
that a woman named Nico Robin
can figure out how to
restore the weapon then the
world needs these blueprints
To be able to fight back
if i continue to keep them
with me even if they threaten
my life i won't hand them
over to the government.
Are you sure?
You know me.
What if I decide to build it?
Do you really think that you can trust me?
I'm giving them to you.
Doesn't that answer your question?
We never change, do we?
Every time we meet face to face,
we yell and argue with each other.
I won't forgive you.
And you may feel the
same way about me, too.
Franky, I'm...
I'm really...
I'm so glad that you're still alive.
You listen to me!
I'm not going to leave this island!
You got that ice for brains!
I'm going to do whatever
the hell I want to do!
You think I'm going to
do what you tell me?
I'd rather die! Understand?
Damn it, Flunky!
We've heard that Tom was
an excellent craftsman
and a creative genius but he was also an
uncontrollable fish man
with superhuman strength
when we ask the citizens
here about him they don't
really have much to say
it must be difficult to
apprentice under a man
like that right Cutty Flam
that ridiculous question
doesn't even deserve a
reply you government goons are
all piles of crap? Easy! Easy?
During that incident, more
than a hundred people,
including Marines and Navy officers,
were severely injured here in Water 7.
And the culprit behind it was you.
Causing the world government that
much trouble is a serious crime.
But because you were confirmed dead in
a C-train accident later that same day,
all of the charges
against you were annulled.
Since you're actually still alive, you'll
be taken to Eni's lobby as a criminal.
There, you can take your time
answering this one simple question.
Where are the secret blueprints for
the ancient weapon known as Pluton?
Now, Bruno... Right.
I was just able to get a connection.
When I reported our latest findings
on this case to our superior,
he said that he wanted to speak
with you directly and immediately.
Superior, huh?
All right, Chief, go
ahead. Hot! Hot! Ouch! Out!
I spilled coffee all over myself, damn it!
Stupid coffee!
What the heck?
So, you're still alive.
Greetings, Cutty Flam.
Long time no see.
It's hard to believe you somehow
managed to survive the accident.
Hard to believe, but
good news nonetheless.
Nevertheless, for the past eight
years, every time my scars hurt,
I was tormented by an
unquenchable anger that
I couldn't take the proper
vengeance I deserved.
Because the criminal responsible
for those scars was dead, you see.
Is that so?
Who are you?
Don't you remember me?
I'm the man from Cipher pool number
five that arrested Tom's workers when I
caught them red-handed for savagely
attacking the judicial ship eight years ago
You're that Spanda guy,
aren't you? Spandam!
You're missing the M!
But I'll have plenty of time to drill that
into your head once you
arrive at Eni's lobby.
Make it quick, men!
I'm simply dying to teach
that criminal a lesson!
Damn stupid lamp.
Tie him up.
Hey punk, watch those hands!
Come on!
Let him go.
No!
Come back here, you bastards!
I'm sorry.
Hey!
If you're not gonna help,
then don't get my hoops up!
Wade, I know you, don't I?
You're part of the Straw Hat crew.
So good!
The wind is too strong!
It's getting worse!
If Iceberg's in there,
we've got to get him out!
Now!
Iceberg!
Paulie!
Nami, oh, no.
I have to treat her right away.
If I can just...
Hurry!
They need first aid.
They're burned all over.
Hey, what are we going
to do with this reindeer?
Help him.
He's saying they're lies. You're right.
Hey, someone give me a hand.
Oh, boy.
That's just sad.
So what you're saying is
that you left the Straw Hats,
but you haven't given
up your life of crime.
What a shame.
If you're a pirate, you're
coming with us, Khalifa. Got it.
And as for this ship, you still
haven't disposed of it? Stay away!
Don't you dare touch her!
Are you listening to me?
What are you doing?
Even if it was only a temporary disguise,
we are still respected as shipwrights.
When we say your ship's done for, then
you would do well to listen to us.
Why do you care?
It's not even your ship!
I can do whatever I want with it!
This lever releases the water, right?
Cut it out!
That's not funny, dammit!
No, stop it!
Don't let her fall!
Don't worry.
I'll carry everyone for
a little bit longer.
You idiot, run!
Oh, damn it!
Is there anything we can do?
Look! Mr. Iceberg's awake!
All right, he's safe!
I knew he'd make it!
That reindeer saved
his life! Are you sure?
I thought it belonged to the Straw Hacks!
Hey, look!
This woman's from the Straw Hats, too!
So, what now?
Do you think maybe we should
tie her up and question her?
I don't know.
She's just a girl.
And she's hurt, too.
I know, but...
Whoa!
You shouldn't be moving yet, Mr.
Iceberg!
Sorry, men, but I need a
little space right now.
That is to say, I want to
speak to this woman in private.
Wonder what those two are talking about?
Beats me.
What was that for?
Stop standing there and give me a hand!
I know Iceberg and Paulie are sick,
but the rest of the Foreman
might still be trapped inside.
Yeah, he's right. Let's go.
Oh, but yeah, sorry.
Well, first off, I must apologize.
I falsely accused your entire crew.
I'll try to clear that up soon.
But for now, I want to
talk about Nico Robin.
What do you know?
When you first came to Water 7?
Did she start acting strangely?
Yeah, she did.
She went into town that day
and then never came back.
By the next morning, she was the prime
suspect in your attempted murder.
When Sanji and Chopper
finally saw her again,
she said this was goodbye and wouldn't
be a part of the crew anymore.
Of course, none of that
made any sense to us,
so we decided to break into
your mansion in hopes that we'd
be able to see her one more
time and find out the truth.
I did it to make my wish come true.
One that can't happen as
long as we're together.
If you can't accept that, I'm sorry.
What kind of wish would
force her to give up all
of her friends I think I
know the answer actually
This probably started shortly after you
lost sight of her for the first time
Cape the government had begun its
operation the moment she arrived
In other words there's a
good reason why your friend
did what she did But before
I go into the details,
I want you to understand that both
Nico Robin and I have the means to
revive an ancient weapon that is
capable of destroying the entire world.
A weapon? That's right.
It's me.
We've hit a snag in the plan.
Everyone head to the bedroom immediately.
Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
Do you understand now?
The blueprints that they found are fake.
I don't care.
I would rather die than hand over
that information to the government.
But now it's not that simple.
If you've decided that
you're going to help them,
and you're searching for
the Poneglyphs yourself,
then I have to do everything
I can to stop you!
I understand your concern,
but I'm only studying the Poneglyphs to
learn more about the history of the world.
I don't care about the weapon.
You have to take responsibility!
I told you this would
happen, but you don't listen.
Franky, even if you weren't trying
to, weapons are made to hurt people.
Whether you want them to or
not, they can hurt your friends.
Even if you don't have malicious intent,
your actions can still hurt people.
If your curiosity for history leads
to the destruction of the world,
then you're better off dying
right here and right now,
Nico Robin!
Even after seeing what happened
to the devils of Ohara,
you still want to walk this path?
You don't know a damn thing about Ohara!
You have no idea how much the world
government has warped my life.
Do you hear me?
If you hate the government
so much, then why help them?
Because I have a wish that I
would sacrifice anything for.
When I came to this town, CP9
presented me with two conditions.
The first was to pin your assassination
on the Straw Hats and leave their crew.
The second was to turn
myself over to the government
and follow their every
order without question.
You realize they won't let you live.
You escaped them for 20 years.
Why would you agree to
something like that now?
In this particular instance,
Cape has been given permission to activate
a Buster Call against the Straw Hats.
A Buster Call?
It's an emergency order
that summons five Vice
-Admirals and ten battleships
to the same location.
no matter how strong you
are no one can survive
a full-scale military
attack of that caliber
under normal circumstances only the
three admirals and the head of the
navy the fleet admiral are allowed
to exercise that kind of authority
however this is a special case just
this once admiral aokiji has given
cp9 the right to make the call when
i heard his name i surrendered.
If I hadn't agreed to their conditions,
then me and the rest of the straw
hats would have been annihilated.
For the past 20 years, I've been able to
run away and survive, no matter what the
circumstance.
That's only because I
had nothing to protect.
Because I was willing to betray
others and use them as a shield.
But not now.
For the first time in all
these years, I can't do that.
But, they picked up the life I gave up on,
returned the heart I lost, and continued
the dreams that I no longer believed in.
Even after all I've done, I've found
friends who will still believe in me.
I see.
But then what is your wish?
That excluding me all
of the other Straw Hat
pirates will be allowed
to leave this island.
Safely and as long as
you have that you don't
care what happens to
the rest of the world?
I don't I've heard all that I can take!
In the end I couldn't pull the trigger.
She was willing to sacrifice the
lives of everyone in this world.
Even her own.
As long as she could save the six of you.
She was protecting us.
As much as I hate to admit it, I
have no right to criticize her.
If they find the blueprints
now, it's all my fault.
Hey, what's wrong?
I'm happy, that's all.
I was so worried.
I didn't want to believe she betrayed us.
I gotta find everyone
else and let them know.
Thank you, Iceberg. Hold on!
What are you going to do now?
The Straw Hats have already lost to CP9
What do you mean we lost?
We haven't even started fighting yet.
We wouldn't be here right
now if we gave up that easy!
Luffy will get Robin back, you'll see.
We just needed motivation, that's all.
Now that we know Robin needs saving?
There's no limit to
what we can accomplish.
Chopper!
Great news!
Come on, Chopper! Wake up!
We have to find everyone!
You can sleep when you're dead!
We gotta get moving before
they take Robin away for good!
Hey, Chopper.
Go meet up with Luffy
and the others and tell
them everything that happened
between us and Robin.
I don't want you to
leave out a single word.
As for me, let's just say I have a plan.
I'll try to be careful.
We'll meet up later.
Something wrong?
Do you think Robin
doesn't like us anymore?
Chopper, let me share a secret with you.
When a woman tells a lie,
a real man forgives her.
Attention, all passengers boarding
today's final service to Enies Lobby.
Due to the current water level,
we will be departing from the
platform on the second floor.
Boarding time is 11 p .m.
Let's go see who they are.
Yeah!
This is a top-secret
operation we'll run in here.
The agents must board in private. No fair.
How considerate of you to
finally turn yourself in.
Twenty years is a long time to run.
Bingo.